♪ I'M GOING DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA HAVE MYSELF
A TIME ♪
FRIENDLY FACES EVERWHERE HUMBLE
FOLKS WITHOUT TEMPTATION
♪ GOING DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA LEAVE
MY WOE'S BEHIND ♪
♪ AMPLE PARKING
DAY OR NIGHT ♪
♪ PEOPLE SPOUTING
"HOWDY NEIGHBOR" ♪
♪ HEADED ON
UP TO SOUTHPARK ♪
♪ GONNA SEE IF
I CAN'T UNWIND ♪
( mumbling )
♪ SO COME ON DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ AND MEET SOME
FRIENDS OF MINE ♪
OH MY GOD,
THEY KILLED KENNY !
YOU BASTARDS !
WHAT THE HELL
IS THAT THING ?
IT LOOKS
LIKE A UFO.
THERE'S NO SUCH
THING AS UFOs.
( sirens )
LETS GET HIM TO THE MORGUE
HEY, WAIT TIL
YOU GUYS SEE
MY HALLOWEEN
COSTUME TOMORROW.
IT KICKS ASS.
DUDE, IT CAN'T BE
COOLER THAN MINE.
WE OUGHT
TO GET HOME
AND GET OUR
COSTUMES READY.
YOU KNOW, I THINK DEATH IS LEAST
FUNNY WHEN IT HAPPENS TO A CHILD
YEAH I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN
MARTY, DO YOU HAVE TO PUT THAT
STUFF ON EVERYTHING?
I DON'T KNOW, IT JUST MAKES
EVERYTHING TASTE SO ENGLISH
WELL, LETS LET HIM DRAIN
SO THE NECROPHELIAC SAYS "IF
THIS ISN'T A CADAVER..."
AHH! GODDAM THAT LITTLE TURD BIT
ME
ME TOO
HA HA, YOU LOOK LIKE A PANSY!
SHUT UP KYLE !
WHAT ARE YOU
SUPPOSED TO BE ?
I'M RAGGEDY ANDY.
WHY THE HELL DID YOU DRESS
UP LIKE RAGGEDY ANDY, DUDE ?
WENDY'S GOING
AS RAGGEDY ANN
AND SHE SAID THAT WAY WE'D WIN
THE COSTUME CONTEST FOR SURE
NO WAY DUDE
I'M GONNA WIN
THE COSTUME CONTEST
WITH THIS SWEET
CHEWBACCA COSTUME.
WENDY SAID THAT FIRST PRIZE
IS TWO TONS OF CANDY.
WOW, COOL !
HEY DUDES...
CARTMAN, WHAT KIND OF
COSTUME IS THAT ?
IT'S ADOLF HITLER COSTUME,
SIEG HEIL, SIEG HEIL !
WHERE'D YOU GET THAT?
MY MOM MADE IT,
ISN'T IT COOL ?
NO, IT'S NOT COOL.
WHAT ARE YOU SUPPOSED
TO BE STAN, HOWDY DOODY ?
NO, I'M RAGGEDY ANDY,
FAT ASS.
OH WOW, YOU LOOK PRETTY COOL..HA
HA
I'LL KICK
YOU LOOK PRETTY CYOUR ASS KYLE !
LOOK OUT,
HOLLY HOBBY'S
ALL PISSED OFF.
HEY LOOK,
KENNY'S NOT DEAD.
YOU FORGOT TO WEAR A COSTUME
KENNY
YEAH, WHAT'S
THE MATTER ?
COULDN'T YOUR FAMILY AFFORD A
COSTUME?
YEAH, WHY IS YOUR FAMILY SO POOR
KENNY?
KENNY'S FAMILY IS SO POOR
THAT...
YESTERDAY, THEY HAD TO PUT THEIR
CARDBOARD BOX UP FOR A SECOND
MORTGAGE
HEH HEH HEH HEH
I SAID YOUR FAMILY HAD TO PUT A
CARDBOARD
BOX UP FOR A SECOND MORTGAGE!
KENNY!
I'M TALKING TO YOU KENNY!
ACHTUNG !
POOR PIECE OF CRAP
COME ON,
WE'RE RUNNING LATE !
WE'RE ALWAYS RUNNING
LATE YOU UGLY SCANK.
WHAT DID YOU SAY ?
I SAID I CAN'T WAIT
TO OWN A FISHING TANK.
OH, NEITHER CAN I.
VERY INTERESTING.
WHAT IS IT,
DOC ?
WELL YOUR TEMPERATURE
IS ONLY 55 DEGREES,
YOU HAVE NO PULSE,
NO HEARTBEAT.
AND YOUR EYES ARE
ALL PUFFY AND STICKY.
OH NO,
YOU MEAN...
YEAH, I'M AFRAID THE TWO
OF YOU HAVE PINK EYE.
I'D GIVE YOU A
TOPICAL MEDICINE
BUT I DON'T WANT
TO TOUCH YOU.
I'M SO HUNGRY
AND ALL I CAN THINK
ABOUT EATING IS...
BRAINS !
WELL FOR GOD SAKE,
DON'T TOUCH YOUR EYES .
I'LL PRESCRIBE
SOME ANTIBIOTICS.
JUST WAIT TIL EVERYONE SEES MY
SWEET CHEWBACCA COSTUME
THEY'RE GONNA
BE SO JEALOUS.
WHOA, DUDE !
EVERYONE CAME
AS CHEWBACCA ?!
IT SURE DOES SEEM TO BE A
POPULAR COSTUME THIS YEAR KYLE.
DAMMIT!
WENDY ?!
HI STAN.
YOU SAID WE WERE GOING TO
BE RAGGEDY ANN AND ANDY.
REMEMBER ?
YEAH.
WE WERE GONNA ENTER THE
COSTUME CONTEST AS A PAIR.
I KNOW.
BUT THEN I REALIZED
HOW STUPID WE WOULD LOOK.
YOU WHAT ?!
I THOUGHT YOU WOULD REACH
THE SAME CONCLUSION SO,
I CAME AS CHEWBACCA.
HEY STAN,
YOU LOOK ALMOST PRETTY
ENOUGH TO KISS.
YEAH, YOU WANT TO
BE MY GIRLFRIEND ?
ALL OF A SUDDEN MY COSTUME
IS PRETTY BAD ASS, HUH ?
DUDE, DRESSING UP LIKE
HITLER IS NOT BAD ASS.
YOU'RE JUST JEALOUS.
WHY DON'T YOU GO BACK TO
ENDOR, YOU STUPID WOOKIE.
WOOKIES DON'T
LIVE ON ENDOR !
( shrieking )
WELL AT LEAST MY MOM'S
NOT ON THE COVER
OF "CRACK WHORE"
MAGAZINE !
WHAT DID YOU SAY ?!
OKAY, NOW ALL YOU
LITTLE CHEWBACCAS
TAKE YOUR SEATS.
CHILDREN, SINCE TODAY
IS HALLOWEEN,
I THOUGHT WE SHOULD LEARN
SOMETHING ABOUT
THE GREAT HORROR WRITER JACKIE
COLLINS
YOU SEE, WHEN JACKIE COLLINS
FIRST WROTE HER NOVEL
EWW!
IS THERE A PROBLEM KENNY!?
lETS TRY TO KEEP OUR ARMS TO
OURSELVES OKAY ?
I'M NEVER GONNA WIN
THAT TWO TONS OF CANDY
LOOKING LIKE
EVERYBODY ELSE.
♪ I'M GONNA DECORATE
THE HOUSE FOR HALLOWEEN
WITH SCARY GHOSTS AND BATS AND
CREEPY CRAWLY THEMES
HELLO THERE, HAPPY HALLOWEEN.
MUST EAT BRAINS
♪ IT'S THE MOST WONDERFUL
TIME OF THE YEAR ♪
♪ DOO-DOO-DOO-DOO... ♪
I'M GONNA MAKE A NEW
COSTUME DURING RECESS.
I CAN STILL
WIN THAT CANDY.
HEY KENNY, ARE YOU
GONNA EAT YOUR PUDDING ?
NO ERIC, GO AHEAD
AND EAT MY PUDDING
IF YOU'D LIKE.
WHY THANK YOU KENNY,
HOW NICE OF YOU.
AREN'T YOU
HUNGRY KENNY ?
HE HASN'T MOVED
AN INCH OR SAID ANYTHING.
HELLO CHILDREN.
HEY CHEF.
WHAT IN THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING
DRESSED UP LIKE THAT ?
EATING KENNY'S
PUDDING.
HELLO THERE,
CHILDREN.
LOVE THE ELVIS
COSTUME CHEF.
ELVIS ?
I'M EVEL KENEVEL !
WHY THE HELL WOULD I
DRESS UP LIKE ELVIS ?
WHY THE HELL WOULD YOU
DRESS UP LIKE EVIL KENEVEL ?!
ANYWAY, I HOPE THAT
YOU KIDS ARE...
ERIC, GOD BLESS IT !
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING ?!
HE SAID I COULD
HAVE HIS PUDDING,
ASK HIM YOURSELF.
THAT'S RIGHT,
PRINCIPAL VICTORIA,
IT'S OKAY WITH ME
BECAUSE ERIC IS COOL.
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT
COSTUME YOUNG MAN ?
MY MOM MADE IT.
SIEG HEIL,
SIEG HEIL !
SHH...
...GOD BLESS
AMERICA.
YOU GET INTO MY OFFICE
BEFORE ANYONE ELSE SEES YOU.
I HAVE TO SHOW YOU
AN EDUCATIONAL VIDEO.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE
YOU BIT MY ARM !
OH GOOD, KENNY'S BACK TO NORMAL
WATCH THE VIDEO ERIC.
Adolf Hitler was
a very, very naughty man.
( German )
PPPPA
So remember kids...
DRESING UP LIKE HITLER IN
SCHOOL, ISN'T COOL
NOW, DO YOU HAVE
ANY QUESTIONS ?
CAN I SEE THAT AGAIN,
THAT WAS COOL !
YOU MUST REMOVE
THAT COSTUME IMMEDIATELY.
I CAN'T, I HAVE TO WIN
THOSE TWO TONS OF CANDY.
WELL HOW ABOUT WE MAKE
YOU A NEW COSTUME ?
LET'S SEE NOW,
UH-HUH...
THOUGHT OF
SOMETHING.
HOW ABOUT WE MAKE YOU A
NICE SCARY GHOST COSTUME ?
AND LET ME JUST MAKE A FEW
QUICKY ALTERATIONS...
AND THERE YOU GO
YOUNG MAN.
LOOKS LIKE THEY GOT
A TOUCH OF THAT PINK EYE
THAT'S GOING AROUND.
BOO, I'M A GHOST.
OH MAN, I FEEL
LIKE A TOTAL CHOAD.
C'MON STAN,
MAYBE THAT'S JUST
BECAUSE YOU LOOK
LIKE A TOTAL CHOAD.
HELLO CHILDREN.
HEY CHEF.
AHH !
WHOA'S REALLY
SCARED OF GHOSTS, HUH ?
WHERE'S KYLE ?
CHECK THIS OUT.
WHOA DUDE !
WHAT IS THAT ?
I'M THE WHOLE
SOLAR SYSTEM.
THE PLANETS EVEN
REVOLVE THE RIGHT WAY.
THAT TUB OF CANDY
IS AS GOOD AS MINE.
OKAY CHILDREN,
LET'S GET YOU LINED UP
SO THE JUDGE CAN GET A GOOD LOOK
AT YOUR STUPID LITTLE COSTUMES
THIS YEAR WE HAVE
A CELEBRITY JUDGE,
THE STAR OF
"FAMILY TIES",
MISS TINA YOTHERS.
WHO? I THOUGHT SHE WAS DEAD
YEAH, ME TOO.
THANK YOU MISS YOTHERS
OKAY, THE SECOND PLACE AWARD FOR
BEST COSTUME GOES TO...
KENNY! FOR HIS EDWARD JAMES
ALMOS COSTUME
AND THE AWARD FOR THE VERY BEST
COSTUME GOES TO..
WENDY! FOR HER CHEWBACCA
COSTUME
WHAT!? BUT SHE LOOKS JUST
LIKE EVERBODY ELSE.
UP YOURS,
TINA YOTHERS !
AND THE AWARD FOR WORSE
COSTUME THIS YEAR GOES TO...
STAN, FOR HIS STUPID LITTLE
CLOWN THING COSTUME
LETS ALL POINT AT STAN AND LAUGH
CHILDREN
HA HA HA HA HA
THANKS A LOT
WENDY,
YOU RUINED
MY HALLOWEEN.
RELAX STAN,
YOU'LL FEEL BETTER ONCE
WE'RE OUT TRICK OR TREATING.
I DON'T WANT TO
TRICK OR TREAT WITH YOU,
YOU LIED TO ME !
OKAY CHILDREN,
LET'S ALL GATHER AROUND AND
BOB FOR STUPID APPLES NOW.
YOU GO FIRST BEBE,
THAT'S GOOD.
JUST USE THOSE
MOUTH MUSCLES
LIKE THE GIRLS
IN BEJING.
BRAINS !
WAIT YOUR TURN,
CLYDE !
DAMN JOHNSON,
WHAT THE HELL
GOT INTO YOU?
PINK EYE
GET THE HELL OUT
OF HERE, JOHNSON.
I DON'T WANT
NO GODAMN PINK EYE.
And The President
responded to the incident
by saying, quote,
"Screw those
commie bastards,
and screw their little
wussy space station."
In other news,
a pink eye epidemic is sweeping
the town of South Park.
Here with a live report,
is a midget
wearing a bikini.
Thanks Tom.
Already more than
half the town's people
here in South Park
have been infected
with the pink eye virus.
Symptomsnclude a complete
loss of heart functions,
blood pressure,
lung activity,
and of course,
sticky puffy eyes.
PINK EYE MY ASS.
I'VE SEEN THIS KIND
OF THING BEFORE.
WHERE THE HELL
IS KYLE ?
WE DON'T HAVE ALL NIGHT
TO WAIT FOR HIM.
I BET I GET MORE
CANDY THAN YOU DUDE.
ARE YOU CRAZY ?
I'M THE CANDY MASTER.
NO, NO, YOU'RE
THE ASS MASTER.
THERE'S
A DIFFERENCE.
HEY, I'M NOT THE ONE
WHO WALKED AROUND ALL DAY
LOOKING LIKE
PIPPY LONGSTOCKING !
WELL AT LEAST MY MOM'S
NOT ON THE COVER
OF "CRACK WHORE"
MAGAZINE !!
GODAMMIT, MY MOM
IS NOT ON THE COVER
OF "CRACK WHORE"
MAGAZINE !
HEY DUDES.
OH GOOD,
YOU'RE HERE.
NOW LET'S MAKE SURE
WE GOT EVERYTHING.
FLASHLIGHT ?
PLASTIC
PUMPKIN PAILS ?
CHECK
TASERS.
WHAT'S THAT ?
FOR SHOCKING PEOPLE
WHO TRY TO GIVE US
GRANOLA TREATS
OR SOMETHING.
YEAH, GRANOLA
PISSES ME OFF.
HEY KENNY.
YOU STINK, KENNY !
YOU STILL DIDN'T GET
A COSTUME, KENNY ?
TOO BAD DRINKING SCOTCH
ISN'T A PAYING JOB,
OR ELSE KENNY'S DAD
WOULD BE A MILLIONAIRE !
I SAID YOUR DAD WOULD
BE A MILLIONAIRE !!
KENNY !
YOUR FAMILY
IS POOR KENNY,
IS POOR !
I DON'T LIKE
KENNY ANYMORE.
HE JUST DOESN'T
COMMUNICATE.
HI GUYS.
HI WENDY.
HOW'S YOUR BARREL
FULL OF CANDY, WENDY ?
I DIDN'T WANT ALL
THAT SWEET STUFF.
I GAVE IT AWAY TO HUNGRY
CHILDREN IN NAIROBI.
YOU WHAT !?
ARE YOU INSANE ?
LET'S GO
TRICK OR TREAT.
I DON'T THINK
SO WENDY.
I THINK YOU HAD
ENOUGH CANDY
FOR ONE DAY.
STAN, I'M SORRY YOU GOT
DRESSED UP LIKE RAGGEDY ANDY.
PLEASE DON'T
BE MAD.
HOW COULD HE BE MAD
WITH SUCH PRETTY HAIR
AND ROSY CHEEKS ?!
TRICK OR TREAT
WITH YOURSELF, WENDY.
BUT STAN...
NO BUTS WENDY,
I WISH YOU WERE DEAD !
AHH !
DOCTOR !
WHY HELLO, CHEF.
LET ME GUESS,
PINK EYE, RIGHT ?
NO, NO DOCTOR.
I'VE SEEN THIS
TYPE OF THING BEFORE.
THIS AIN'T NO PINK EYE,
IT'S THE LIVING DEAD !
WHAT THE HELL ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT ?
THINK ABOUT IT.DEAD PEOPLE
GETTING UP AND WALKING AROUND
AND TINA YOTHERS COMING TO TOWN.
COINCIDENCE?
OH I DON'T THINK SO
CHEF, I THINK THAT MAYBE THE
PINK EYE HAS MADE YOU A
LITTLE DELIRIOUS.
LET ME GIVE YOU
SOME TOPICAL CREAM.
DAMMIT,
DON'T YOU SEE ?!
THESE PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN ZOMBIEFIED.
THEY GOT NO HEARTBEAT,
NO FEELING.
I'LL SHOW YOU.
AHH !
MR. TORRES WAS HERE FOR
A ROUTINE CHECK UP, CHEF.
OH, SORRY.
BUT MY POINT IS
THAT TOPICAL CREAM
AIN'T GONNA FIX
WHAT'S WRONG HERE.
HEY NOW.
THERE HAVE BEEN A LOT OF
INCREDIBLE ADVANCES
IN TOPICAL CREAMS
OVER THE LAST FEW YEARS.
DOCTOR, WHO WAS
THE FIRST PERSON
TO COME IN HERE
WITH THE SICKNESS ?
WELL, IT WAS THE MORTICIAN
AND HIS ASSISTANT
AT THE MORGUE.
AHH !
NOW, NOW, FELLAS,
LET'S FORM A LINE.
I'VE GOT ENOUGH TOPICAL
CREAM FOR EVERYBODY.
TRICK OR TREAT !
OH, HOW CUTE.
AHH !
DUDE, KENNY !
OH MY GOD,
CALL 911 !!
NICE GOING KENNY
SHE WAS ABOUT TO GIVE US CANDY
YEAH, SHE HAD SWEETY POPS
YOU OWE ME A
SWEETIE POP, ASSHOLE.
MAYOR, WE'VE GOT
A BIG PROBLEM.
WHY CHEF,
WHAT A SURPRISE.
YOU'RE PROBABLY WONDERING
WHY WE'RE STANDING HERE
WITH A PILE OF MONEY
AND NO PANTS ON.
ACTUALLY...
I CAN ASSURE YOU THAT
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH THE
JAPANESE MAFIA.
NOT A THINGY-DINGY.
I DON'T REALLY
GIVE A CRAP !
WE'VE GOT TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT THE LIVING DEAD !
YOU MEAN
TINA YOTHERS ?!
NO DAMMIT,
I'M TALKING ABOUT
THE ZOMBIES THAT HAVE
TAKEN OVER SOUTH PARK.
WELL EVEL, WHY DON'T
YOU JUMP OVER THEM
WITH YOUR
ROCKET CYCLE ?
THE HELL
WITH YOU BOTH !
WELL, LET'S
GET BACK TO IT.
RIGHTO.
TRICK OR TREAT !
HOPE YOU KIDS LIKE
CHOCOLATE PEANUT BUTTER
CREAM PUFFIES...
AHH !
GET IT OFF,
GET IT OFF ME !
DAMMIT !
WE'LL NEVER
GET ANY CANDY
IF KENNY KEEPS
EATING PEOPLE !
YEAH, THAT'S
IT KENNY.
YOU CAN'T TRICK OR TREAT
WITH US ANYMORE.
TRICK TREAT !
HEY.
THEY'RE ALL DRESSED UP
LIKE GHOSTS TOO.
ONE TOOTIE BAR ?
YOU CHEAP BASTARDS !
( screaming )
TRICK OR TREAT !
GET OFF MY PROPERTY,
YOU BRAIN EATING
ZOMBIE BASTARDS !
NO !
CHEF !              CHEF !
SORRY CHILDREN,
I THOUGHT YOU
WERE ONE OF THEM.
CAN WE HAVE SOME
CANDY NOW PLEASE ?
DAMMIT BOY,
WHAT IN THE HELL ARE YOU
DOING DRESSED UP LIKE THAT ?
I'M TRYING TO
TRICK OR TREAT, GODAMMIT !
REMIND ME TO
WHIP YOUR ASS GOOD
THE NEXT TIME
I SEE YOU !
NOW GET IN HERE BEFORE
THOSE ZOMBIES GET YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, CHEF ?
ZOMBIES, CHILDREN.
SOUTH PARK IS OVERRUN
WITH THE LIVING DEAD.
HAVEN'T YOU NOTICED
ANYTHING STRANGE LATELY ?
NOT REALLY
EXCEPT THAT
KENNY KEEPS EATING
PEOPLE'S BRAINS.
DON'T YOU CHILDREN SEE ?
KENNY'S TURNED
INTO A ZOMBIE !
ALONG WITH
EVERYONE ELSE IN TOWN.
OH MY GOD,
THAT MEANS...
IF EVERYONE'S TURNED
INTO ZOMBIES,
THEN THERE WON'T BE
ANYONE TO GIVE US CANDY !PP
CHEF, YOU'VE GOT
TO HELP US !
I'M WORKING
ON IT CHILDREN.
WAIT, WHERE
ARE WE GOING ?
THE DOCTOR SAID THE FIRST
PEOPLE HE TREATED
WERE THE MORTICIAN
AND HIS ASSISTANT.
I'VE GOT A HUNCH WE'LL
GET TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS
AT THE MORGUE.
( farting )
THAT WAS KYLE.
I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THIS CHEF.
YEAH,
I'M SCARED.
REMEMBER CANDY,
FOCUS ON THE CANDY.
WHAT ARE WE
DOING HERE CHEF ?
JUST LOOK FOR ANYTHING
SUSPICIOUS.
( Kyle )
I FOUND IT,
I FOUND IT !
WHAT?
SEE CARTMAN, YOUR MOM IS ON THE
COVER
WE TOLD YOU DUDE
YOU BETTER LET ME TAKE THAT
KYLE
HEY CHEF, LOOK
I GOTTA CALL THIS HOTLINE
NUMBETR CHILDREN
PINKEYE...
IT'S THE BRITISH KID,
HE'A A LITTLE LYMIE
ZOMBIE NOW
AHH! LOOK OUT CHILDREN
AHHH...AHHH
GRRR...GRRR..
OKAY CHEF, DIAL THE
HOTLINE NUMBER
CHEF?.... CHEF
CHEF!!
♪ I'M GONNA
MAKE LOVE ♪
♪ EVEN WHEN I'M DEAD ♪
♪ MY BODY MIGHT
GET COLD ♪
♪ BUT IT'S ALWAYS
HOT IN MY BED, MAKE LOVE
♪ DON'T YOU
BE AFRAID ♪
♪ JUST BECAUSE MY HEART
AIN'T BEATING ♪
♪ IT DON'T MEAN
YOU WON'T GET LAID ♪
WHOO-HOO !
LETS GET OUT OF HERE!
HEY, THERE'S
A PAY PHONE
YOU CALL
THE NUMBER KYLE.
BUT THE ZOMBIES ARE COMING
WE'LL HOLD THEM OFF
customer service
hot line.
For Worcestershire
sauce recipes,
press one followed
by the pound sign.
For Worcestershire
product placement,
please press two.
If Worcestershire
sauce has been used
as embalming,
please press...
NOBODY SCREWS UP
MY TRICK OR TREATING
AND GETS AWAY
WITH IT !
COOL !
SWEET !
Worchestershire sauce emergency
hotline
This call might
be monitored
to ensure you the
highest quality service.
How may
I help you ?
THERE'S A BUNCH
OF ZOMBIES HERE.
Please hold.
WENDY? AHHH! FINISH HER, DUDE,
SHE'S A ZOMBIE NOW.
I KNOW, BUT...
BUT...
C'MON STAN,
REMEMBER HOW SHE DISSED YOU
AT THE COSTUME CONTEST ?
YEAH.
The regular sauce,
the first thing
you need to do
IS MAKE SURE THAT
YOU DO NOT JUST GO OUT
AND START DECAPITATING
ZOMBIES LEFT AND RIGHT.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ?
DO NOT START
DECAPITATING
zombies left
and right.
OKAY, THEN WHAT ?
WENDY, I KNOW
WE HAD A FIGHT
AND I DID WISHED
YOU WERE DEAD,
BUT I DIDN'T
MEAN IT.
KILL HER, STAN.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS KILL
THE ORIGINAL ZOMBIE.
THE ONE THAT STARTED
THE WHOLE MESS.
ONCE YOU KILLED
THE ORIGINAL ZOMBIE,
ALL THE OTHER ZOMBIES
WILL TURN BACK TO NORMAL.
ORIGINAL ZOMBIE ?
HOW THE HELL DO WE KNOW
WHO THE ORIGINAL ZOMBIE IS ?
WE REALIZE YOU
HAVE A CHOICE IN
WORCESTERSHIRE SAUCES,
WE ARE DELIGHTED THAT...
WAIT A MINUTE,
THAT THING LANDED ON KENNY
AND THEY TOOK HIM
TO THE MORTUARY.
I CAN'T.
OH MY GOD,
I KILLED KENNY !
YOU BASTARD!
WHAT HAPPENED? STAN?
DON'T WORRY BABE, EVERYTHING'S
GONNA BE OKAY
THEY'RE TURNING
BACK TO NORMAL.
YOU DID IT
CHILDREN !
OKAY, LETS GO TICK OR
TREATING NOW, C'MOM!
I'M SORRY I DISSED YOU
AT SCHOOL LIKE THAT
STAN,
I GUESS I JUST WASN'T VERYO
CONSIDERATE OF YOUR
FEELINGS.
THAT'S OKAY WENDY.
I'M SORRY I WISHED
YOU WERE DEAD.
MAYBE WE CAN ACTUALLY
KISS TONIGHT, STAN.
BLAH!, SICKGROSS STAN
BARF IS GROSS.
OH MAN, I CAN'T
BELIEVE HE'S GONE.
YEAH, HE WAS TOO YOUNG
TO BE TAKEN FROM US.
DUDE, YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO CUT HIM IN HALF
WITH A CHAIN SAW.
LET US REMEMBER
THE GOOD TIMES.
KENNY WOULD
HAVE WANTED IT.
YOU KNOW, I'VE REALLY LEARNED
SOMETHING TODAY
HALLOWEEN ISN'T ABOUT COSTUMES
OR CANDY
IT'S ABOUT BEING GOOD TO ONE
ANOTHER, AND GIVING AND LOVING.
NO DUDE,
THAT'S CHRISTMAS.
OH.
THEN WHAT'S
HALLOWEEN ABOUT ?
COSTUMES AND CANDY.
OH.
WELL LET'S GO HOME AND
START EATING THAT CANDY.
WE CAN EAT IT AT
CARTMAN'S HOUSE
AND SEE MORE NAUGHTY
PICTURES OF HIS MOM.
YEAH.
KNOCK IT OFF
YOU GUYS !
SHE SAID SHE WAS YOUNG
AND NEEDED THE MONEY.
CARTMAN, THOSE PICTURES WERE
TAKEN LIKE LAST MONTH
SCREW YOU GUYS
GRRMPH..GRRMPH